[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "What do we stand for as a country and what do I stand for in my house, with my family?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "we", "stand", "for", "as", "a", "country", "and", "what", "do", "I", "stand", "for", "in", "my", "house", ",", "with", "my", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "His thoughts on the race for the White House.", "answer_tokens": ["His", "thoughts", "on", "the", "race", "for", "the", "White", "House", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Marines"], "TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ":", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "Tell me about what you've been doing here?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "what", "you", "'ve", "been", "doing", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, this morning, I went to -- the Marines took me to a village that they had constructed like an Afghan village.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "morning", ",", "I", "went", "to", "--", "the", "Marines", "took", "me", "to", "a", "village", "that", "they", "had", "constructed", "like", "an", "Afghan", "village", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WP", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "When you are that close and they're firing live ammunition, what's the difference between that and everything you've read or heard about it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "are", "that", "close", "and", "they", "'re", "firing", "live", "ammunition", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "difference", "between", "that", "and", "everything", "you", "'ve", "read", "or", "heard", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Well, I think it made me realize just what our servicemen and women are going through.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "made", "me", "realize", "just", "what", "our", "servicemen", "and", "women", "are", "going", "through", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "What was that like for you as a parent to actually see a son go to war?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "like", "for", "you", "as", "a", "parent", "to", "actually", "see", "a", "son", "go", "to", "war", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Well, I think it was really tough for our family, to have Bo deployed, that whole year was very tough.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "really", "tough", "for", "our", "family", ",", "to", "have", "Bo", "deployed", ",", "that", "whole", "year", "was", "very", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iraq"], "LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"], "PERSON": ["Joe"]}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "How much harder is it that your husband is one of the decision-makers to go into war, to go into battle zones?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "harder", "is", "it", "that", "your", "husband", "is", "one", "of", "the", "decision-makers", "to", "go", "into", "war", ",", "to", "go", "into", "battle", "zones", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "IDEN: Actually, that's one of the best things about it for me because I know that Joe truly wanted to get out of Iraq and he wants to get our soldiers out of Afghanistan as soon as they can be pulled out.", "answer_tokens": ["IDEN", ":", "Actually", ",", "that", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "best", "things", "about", "it", "for", "me", "because", "I", "know", "that", "Joe", "truly", "wanted", "to", "get", "out", "of", "Iraq", "and", "he", "wants", "to", "get", "our", "soldiers", "out", "of", "Afghanistan", "as", "soon", "as", "they", "can", "be", "pulled", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "What are the things you most relate to in terms of the problems or the issues that arise when you have a loved one who's at battle?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "things", "you", "most", "relate", "to", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "problems", "or", "the", "issues", "that", "arise", "when", "you", "have", "a", "loved", "one", "who", "'s", "at", "battle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "TO", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "CD", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "I -- you know, I think -- well, with the Wounded Warriors, when -- my son was not wounded, but when they come back, you know, the mothers sort of pull me aside and you know talk to me privately about, you know, I never thought my son would come back like this and, you know, make these comments to me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "--", "well", ",", "with", "the", "Wounded", "Warriors", ",", "when", "--", "my", "son", "was", "not", "wounded", ",", "but", "when", "they", "come", "back", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "mothers", "sort", "of", "pull", "me", "aside", "and", "you", "know", "talk", "to", "me", "privately", "about", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "never", "thought", "my", "son", "would", "come", "back", "like", "this", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "make", "these", "comments", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "And so they can be almost in visible as military families?", "question_tokens": ["And", "so", "they", "can", "be", "almost", "in", "visible", "as", "military", "families", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "What was the day like when Bo came home?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "day", "like", "when", "Bo", "came", "home", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "That was, you know, a wonderful day.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "wonderful", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "What do you get an overall sense of the mood, the atmosphere amongst people in the service is right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "get", "an", "overall", "sense", "of", "the", "mood", ",", "the", "atmosphere", "amongst", "people", "in", "the", "service", "is", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, I think that -- I think they're uplifted because I think that they know that this administration truly has their back and we're -- they are a number one priority for this administration, to take care of them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "--", "I", "think", "they", "'re", "uplifted", "because", "I", "think", "that", "they", "know", "that", "this", "administration", "truly", "has", "their", "back", "and", "we", "'re", "--", "they", "are", "a", "number", "one", "priority", "for", "this", "administration", ",", "to", "take", "care", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "What were Joe's first words when he came through the door?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "Joe", "'s", "first", "words", "when", "he", "came", "through", "the", "door", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Gosh, I don't remember.", "answer_tokens": ["Gosh", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "remember", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Is it for moments like that everything seems worth it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "for", "moments", "like", "that", "everything", "seems", "worth", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Is this true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, part of it is true.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "part", "of", "it", "is", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Philadelphia"]}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Where was your first date?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "was", "your", "first", "date", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "We went to Philadelphia to the movies.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "went", "to", "Philadelphia", "to", "the", "movies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Do you remember the film?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "the", "film", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Was he so mesmerizing you didn't even -- didn't look at the screen?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "so", "mesmerizing", "you", "did", "n't", "even", "--", "did", "n't", "look", "at", "the", "screen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ":", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "You know, I -- well, you know, I went out with him because -- I actually had another date that night that I canceled and just because I thought he would be interesting to go out with.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "--", "well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "went", "out", "with", "him", "because", "--", "I", "actually", "had", "another", "date", "that", "night", "that", "I", "canceled", "and", "just", "because", "I", "thought", "he", "would", "be", "interesting", "to", "go", "out", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Did you really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "What are the qualities about Joe Biden that you think make him fit to be vice president of this country?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "qualities", "about", "Joe", "Biden", "that", "you", "think", "make", "him", "fit", "to", "be", "vice", "president", "of", "this", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, I think he has a strong character.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "has", "a", "strong", "character", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Obama"]}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "I mean do you get the same kind of treatment that other people do, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "do", "you", "get", "the", "same", "kind", "of", "treatment", "that", "other", "people", "do", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "You know, a lot of my students don't really realize that I'm second lady because they don't either expect it or maybe they haven't watched the news, I don't know, but I can go whole semesters when somebody will say to me, you know what, I saw you on the TV and you were with Michelle Obama, and I screamed to my mom, look, there's my English teacher.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "my", "students", "do", "n't", "really", "realize", "that", "I", "'m", "second", "lady", "because", "they", "do", "n't", "either", "expect", "it", "or", "maybe", "they", "have", "n't", "watched", "the", "news", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "but", "I", "can", "go", "whole", "semesters", "when", "somebody", "will", "say", "to", "me", ",", "you", "know", "what", ",", "I", "saw", "you", "on", "the", "TV", "and", "you", "were", "with", "Michelle", "Obama", ",", "and", "I", "screamed", "to", "my", "mom", ",", "look", ",", "there", "'s", "my", "English", "teacher", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Do you think there is a lot more to be done now with education?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "is", "a", "lot", "more", "to", "be", "done", "now", "with", "education", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 205, "question": "What have been the best and worse things of being the vice president's wife in the last few years?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "been", "the", "best", "and", "worse", "things", "of", "being", "the", "vice", "president", "'s", "wife", "in", "the", "last", "few", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "The best things are, I think that I have a platform and I can do so many things just like you mentioned, with one of the best nights was of course --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "things", "are", ",", "I", "think", "that", "I", "have", "a", "platform", "and", "I", "can", "do", "so", "many", "things", "just", "like", "you", "mentioned", ",", "with", "one", "of", "the", "best", "nights", "was", "of", "course", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "What's been the worst day so far?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "worst", "day", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "The worst day.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "worst", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Are you guys ready for the fight that's coming?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "guys", "ready", "for", "the", "fight", "that", "'s", "coming", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Final question, what does being an American mean to you?", "question_tokens": ["Final", "question", ",", "what", "does", "being", "an", "American", "mean", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Being -- I think it means, you know, having traveled around to other countries and I think the aspect of freedom is really important.", "answer_tokens": ["Being", "--", "I", "think", "it", "means", ",", "you", "know", ",", "having", "traveled", "around", "to", "other", "countries", "and", "I", "think", "the", "aspect", "of", "freedom", "is", "really", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "What are your thoughts about the State of the Union right now in America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "thoughts", "about", "the", "State", "of", "the", "Union", "right", "now", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Well, it's interesting, you know, when we -- in watching the state of the political landscape or the media political landscape -- with the Republican debates.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "we", "--", "in", "watching", "the", "state", "of", "the", "political", "landscape", "or", "the", "media", "political", "landscape", "--", "with", "the", "Republican", "debates", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["State of the Union"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Do you care about any aspect of a politician's private life?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "care", "about", "any", "aspect", "of", "a", "politician", "'s", "private", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "I think the only great skill that he has is in responding to such things or inflaming such things in attacks on others, so it's really gone into his wheelhouse.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "only", "great", "skill", "that", "he", "has", "is", "in", "responding", "to", "such", "things", "or", "inflaming", "such", "things", "in", "attacks", "on", "others", ",", "so", "it", "'s", "really", "gone", "into", "his", "wheelhouse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Do you feel proud to be an American right now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "proud", "to", "be", "an", "American", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Well, yes, I do, because I have -- I always have had a great belief in the possibility here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "do", ",", "because", "I", "have", "--", "I", "always", "have", "had", "a", "great", "belief", "in", "the", "possibility", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "You must have been pleased to see that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "have", "been", "pleased", "to", "see", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Yes, I mean I think it's a complicated situation.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "complicated", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Bush"]}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "CD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "If he was president and you had Ahmadinejad in Iran, and developing nuclear weapons, was it clear intent this publicly states to obliterate Israel, what would you do as president to stop him?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "was", "president", "and", "you", "had", "Ahmadinejad", "in", "Iran", ",", "and", "developing", "nuclear", "weapons", ",", "was", "it", "clear", "intent", "this", "publicly", "states", "to", "obliterate", "Israel", ",", "what", "would", "you", "do", "as", "president", "to", "stop", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Look, I always thought that when 9/11 happened that I would have loved to have seen George Bush, let the American people and the world know, this is inexcusable and these people are going to die, and we're going to kill them.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "always", "thought", "that", "when", "9/11", "happened", "that", "I", "would", "have", "loved", "to", "have", "seen", "George", "Bush", ",", "let", "the", "American", "people", "and", "the", "world", "know", ",", "this", "is", "inexcusable", "and", "these", "people", "are", "going", "to", "die", ",", "and", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "kill", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran", "Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "So you're not a pacifist, are you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'re", "not", "a", "pacifist", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "It's wrong to characterize you in that way?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "wrong", "to", "characterize", "you", "in", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Shall we agree, Sean?", "question_tokens": ["Shall", "we", "agree", ",", "Sean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "I'm right with you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "right", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sean"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "VBN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "CC", ":", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJS", "JJ", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "What have you made of that double pronged phenomenon?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "made", "of", "that", "double", "pronged", "phenomenon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I think that you're seeing the more experienced candidates hanging in and -- and then adopting that kind of fundamentalist position they feel is most sellable now, but that the -- that the candidates that have fallen out were just amateurs among amateurs.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "you", "'re", "seeing", "the", "more", "experienced", "candidates", "hanging", "in", "and", "--", "and", "then", "adopting", "that", "kind", "of", "fundamentalist", "position", "they", "feel", "is", "most", "sellable", "now", ",", "but", "that", "the", "--", "that", "the", "candidates", "that", "have", "fallen", "out", "were", "just", "amateurs", "among", "amateurs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "When you hear that, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "that", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I think the same thing when something happens, whether it was part of the initial campaign commitments of President Obama or maybe something that fell short of that or changed afterwards, that, first, we have to be a country of -- of the people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "same", "thing", "when", "something", "happens", ",", "whether", "it", "was", "part", "of", "the", "initial", "campaign", "commitments", "of", "President", "Obama", "or", "maybe", "something", "that", "fell", "short", "of", "that", "or", "changed", "afterwards", ",", "that", ",", "first", ",", "we", "have", "to", "be", "a", "country", "of", "--", "of", "the", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum"]}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Even though you disagree with him on these core issues, do you have more respect for somebody like him, who at least is consistent on his principles, even if you don't agree with him, than somebody like a Mitt Romney, who is a legendary flip-flopper, apparently changing his principled positions for political expediency?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "though", "you", "disagree", "with", "him", "on", "these", "core", "issues", ",", "do", "you", "have", "more", "respect", "for", "somebody", "like", "him", ",", "who", "at", "least", "is", "consistent", "on", "his", "principles", ",", "even", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "agree", "with", "him", ",", "than", "somebody", "like", "a", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "who", "is", "a", "legendary", "flip-flopper", ",", "apparently", "changing", "his", "principled", "positions", "for", "political", "expediency", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "IN", "JJS", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Yes, if he told me -- if Rick Santorum said that here's what I'm going to do, I'd be much more likely to believe him than many others.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "if", "he", "told", "me", "--", "if", "Rick", "Santorum", "said", "that", "here", "'s", "what", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "do", ",", "I", "'d", "be", "much", "more", "likely", "to", "believe", "him", "than", "many", "others", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "But do you have more respect for politicians who at least are true to themselves?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "have", "more", "respect", "for", "politicians", "who", "at", "least", "are", "true", "to", "themselves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "IN", "JJS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "This is again where words get into our conditioning.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "again", "where", "words", "get", "into", "our", "conditioning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Where are they now?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "they", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Well, in two years, they've gotten to the point where they were able to, against a lot of odds, select a leadership of the people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "two", "years", ",", "they", "'ve", "gotten", "to", "the", "point", "where", "they", "were", "able", "to", ",", "against", "a", "lot", "of", "odds", ",", "select", "a", "leadership", "of", "the", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Newman", "Joanne Woodward"]}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "I am going to ask you this again because it still fascinates me, why somebody like you, Oscar winning superstar, not short of a few dollars, has no need to do this, and certainly not the amount of time you spent -- what really motivates you, Sean Penn, to dedicate so much of your time to this cause?", "question_tokens": ["I", "am", "going", "to", "ask", "you", "this", "again", "because", "it", "still", "fascinates", "me", ",", "why", "somebody", "like", "you", ",", "Oscar", "winning", "superstar", ",", "not", "short", "of", "a", "few", "dollars", ",", "has", "no", "need", "to", "do", "this", ",", "and", "certainly", "not", "the", "amount", "of", "time", "you", "spent", "--", "what", "really", "motivates", "you", ",", "Sean", "Penn", ",", "to", "dedicate", "so", "much", "of", "your", "time", "to", "this", "cause", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "You know, I remember seeing an interview with Paul Newman many years ago, where he was asked, you know, what is it that's kept you in this marriage, in love with Joanne Woodward for all this time.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "remember", "seeing", "an", "interview", "with", "Paul", "Newman", "many", "years", "ago", ",", "where", "he", "was", "asked", ",", "you", "know", ",", "what", "is", "it", "that", "'s", "kept", "you", "in", "this", "marriage", ",", "in", "love", "with", "Joanne", "Woodward", "for", "all", "this", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sean Penn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Ever wake up and think, I wish I was George Clooney?", "question_tokens": ["Ever", "wake", "up", "and", "think", ",", "I", "wish", "I", "was", "George", "Clooney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Clooney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Don't we all?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "we", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Well, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "He's brilliantly cool, isn't he, under pressure?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "brilliantly", "cool", ",", "is", "n't", "he", ",", "under", "pressure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Any best actress tips?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "best", "actress", "tips", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "No, my mother is -- she's an extraordinary actress herself.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "my", "mother", "is", "--", "she", "'s", "an", "extraordinary", "actress", "herself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "So you don't see many movies then?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "do", "n't", "see", "many", "movies", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "ENN: No.", "answer_tokens": ["ENN", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Anything?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Yes, I have some things that I'm playing with and some things I will be doing.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "have", "some", "things", "that", "I", "'m", "playing", "with", "and", "some", "things", "I", "will", "be", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "But to have the willpower to just say no to all of this stuff, to turn down 15 million dollars offers and so on, I mean, this can't be easy?", "question_tokens": ["But", "to", "have", "the", "willpower", "to", "just", "say", "no", "to", "all", "of", "this", "stuff", ",", "to", "turn", "down", "15", "million", "dollars", "offers", "and", "so", "on", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "this", "ca", "n't", "be", "easy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Well, I think you're going a little high.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "you", "'re", "going", "a", "little", "high", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["15 million dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Amid all this, Sean, is there any room for love in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Amid", "all", "this", ",", "Sean", ",", "is", "there", "any", "room", "for", "love", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Yes, there is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "there", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sean"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Anyone in particular?", "question_tokens": ["Anyone", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Well, I'm madly in love with my daughter and my son.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "madly", "in", "love", "with", "my", "daughter", "and", "my", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Did you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "That suggests that maybe --", "answer_tokens": ["That", "suggests", "that", "maybe", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Nothing you want to talk about?", "question_tokens": ["Nothing", "you", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]